Some sagas just won't die.
Vampires Suck is a comedy, fantasy film directed by Aaron Seltzer.
Becca, an anxious, non-vampire teen is torn between two boys.
Before she can choose, Becca must get around her
controlling father, who treats her like a child.
Meanwhile, Becca's friends contend with their own romantic
issues – all of which collide at the prom.
Becca Crane, played by Jenn Proske.
Edward, played by Matt Lanter.
Jacob White, played by Chris Riggi.
Frank Crane, played by Diedrich Bader.
Jennifer, played by Anneliese Van Der Pol.
Daro, played by Ken Jeong.
Vampires Suck is a 2010 American parody film written and
directed by Jason Friedberg and Aaron Seltzer.
It stars Jenn Proske, Matt Lanter, Christopher N.
Riggi, Ken Jeong, Anneliese van der Pol, and Arielle Kebbel.
The film is a parody of The Twilight Saga franchise (mainly
the original film and its sequel, New Moon).
Like the previous Friedberg and Seltzer movies, the film was
panned by critics for its humor and plot.
20th Century Fox theatrically released the film on August 18, 2010.
The film explores themes of high school, vampire, parody, spoof, prom.
The tone is lighthearted.